Don't use the wrong filters. It could
cost you your entire account. Right now,
hundreds of traders are scalping tiny
caps with zero risk management and
blowing up fast. But the smart ones,
they're using sniper level filters to
dodge rugs, avoid insider traps, and
catch instant 3, five, even 10x moves.
In this video, I'm going to show you
exactly how to build the perfect filter
setup across new creations about to
graduate and high volume daily runners
using real examples and exact market cap
thresholds. These are the same filters I
use to build my own daily coin list and
hit backto back profits. If you've never
been too early, too late, or completely
rugged, this is your edge. Do me a
favor, press that like button, and let's
get onto
it. All right, my friends. Today, we're
going to focus on Axiom migrated tab. A
lot of people ask me about the migrated
tab because I've already gave you guys
on the volume strategy everything about
this tab here, the final stretch. When
it comes to new pairs, it's irrelevant.
You should never put any filters there
to be completely honest. But now we're
going to talk about this one here, the
migrated. This category shows the newest
token is hitting the market and to
maximize visibility, your filters need
to be loose, but also protective against
rugs. So here's what I recommend and I'm
going to show you visibly next. At least
one social link. If a coin doesn't have
social, the dev put literally zero
effort. So you should avoid it. Then the
dev holding should be maximum 12%.
Anything more means the dev likely
bought in with more than three soul. And
that's a no no. That's a red flag. Then
when it comes to insider wallet supply,
you want to see maximum 10%. Insider
wallets are those that didn't buy but
were sent tokens. So too many means the
supply is heavily heavily controlled.
And you have to be careful about that.
You want visibility into as many coins
as possible here, but still with filters
that give you safety from blatant scams.
When it comes to volume, you want
minimum 15k, which is enough to avoid
dead coins, but not so high that you're
late or you're not going to see a lot of
these that could run. When it comes to
token age, you want minimum 45 minutes
because it helps you filter out spam and
gives time for early setup migration.
And essentially, these are the measures.
So now let's look right here at the top
on the right you have migrated. Remember
I gave you all the filters when it comes
to final stretch. So when it comes to
migrated, you can mix migrated with
final stretch. If you put together all
these filters, I think you have the
perfect setup to start trading low caps
on axium. So here we are migrated. Look,
when it comes to protocols, you want
pump, you want launch lab, you want
bonk, and you want launch a coin as
well. You don't need dynamic, moonshot,
boop. These are irrelevant for now. Then
when it comes to socials, as I said in
the beginning of the video, you want at
least one social because I mean, if the
dev puts zero effort, why would you even
try and trade the coin? Then when it
comes to metrics here on volume, see
$25,000. So you eliminate all of these
fake volume coins that will get you
rugged. And that's the only thing you
want when it comes to metrics. Now, when
it comes to audit, this is the important
part. age minimum you want 45 minutes
and then when it comes to dev hold
holding you want 12% and there's a
difference if you put 10 12 there's a
big difference there when it comes to
catching runners so I think 12% for 2025
is the number and then when it comes to
insiders you want 10% maximum so maximum
12% dev holding and then maximum
insiders 10% age minimum 45 as I said
previously and if you apply these
filters what you will see is a lot of
the garbage will be cleaned but not all
of it and then if you mix that with the
final stretch that I gave you guys on a
volume strategy which I will leave at
the end of this video and I'll also
leave a link down below so you guys can
watch the volume strategy which gives
you all the final stretch filters that
you need. If you mix these two together,
I think this is where you have basically
the perfect setup to become a profitable
Axium trader. Now, let me give you a
live example of mixing these two
strategies. Okay, so this is the
strategy from the volume strategy that I
gave you on another video which is
basically you have the 69K migration
candle. Look, it migrated. It had the
first pump. It actually had two pumps.
You wait for it to come below. It came
below. Grab some. It comes again. If it
then goes below again, that's when you
load up. Load up on the green candle and
then you can take profits at 100K, 200K,
etc. But here's the reason why these
migrated filters are very important. In
this case that I traded here, Borpa, you
can see it went to like 400K. And so,
how do you know if you should be selling
everything at 120 or if you should leave
a little bit of profits for 300K? These
filters here that I gave you today are
one of the things that you can see to
know if you can actually leave like 10
or 20% of your bag on some of these that
you probably were already watching on
final stretch because with these filters
are migrated you know that the coin can
probably have a little bit more of
potential to do 200k 300k. So boray is a
great example. So volume strategy gives
you the entry, gives you the the perfect
entry trade. And then these migrated
filters let you know if the coin can go
to 200, 300K or a little bit higher. So
that after you exit on that initial pump
at 120K, you know, you see it here,
look, the coin is on migrated. And so
because it's on migrated and all these
metrics that I put there, good volume,
the dev isn't holding too much, insiders
don't have too much. Well, maybe it can
push a little bit higher. And that's why
I give you guys these filters when it
comes to migrator. Okay, these aren't
the most important filters. The most
important ones are the ones on final
stretch on the volume trading strategy.
But these ones are just an add-on. Now,
it's very important to understand this.
I was only able to catch this with a
preset limit order on Axium. So, you
come on Axium, you click limit orders,
you see the strategy, and then you leave
them and you wait for them to get hit.
Okay? And this is the most important
strategy. It's the limit order strategy.
If I had hesitated or if I was using
slower platforms like for example
Jupiter, I would have completely missed
this move. So, here's what I want you to
do. Click the link under this video.
Sign up to Axium. All of my daily
entries and exits are updated live
there. And very soon I'll be opening
private group only for the XM referrals
where I'm going to drop alpha coins,
trades, filters, exact levels I'm
watching, everything you need with more
detail there. But heads up, this group
is free, but is also limited to active
traders using my link. No lurkers, no
latecomers, just alpha sharing savages
trying to outperform the rest of the
market. You now have the exact scalping
filters that separate winners from the
wreck. Most traders are still guessing,
still aping inter rugs. But you, you've
got a framework built on precision,
timing, and edge. So, if you're serious,
hit the like under the video, sign up,
start trading, and I'll see you on the
group when I open it. Thanks for
watching. See you on the next one.
[Music]